export const QAMAdlib = [
  {
    questionId: 1,
    question: "What's the full name of the company, and its mission?",
    contentList: [
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "Full Name: ",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[InnovateX Solutions Inc.]",
        placeholder: "[InnovateX Solutions Inc.]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: `<br/> Mission: To revolutionize`,
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[healthcare] ",
        placeholder: "[healthcare]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "using",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[AI-driven diagnostics]",
        placeholder: "[AI-driven diagnostics]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "for",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[faster, more accurate results]",
        placeholder: "[faster, more accurate results]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: ". Our mission focuses on integrating",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[innovative technologies]",
        placeholder: "[innovative technologies]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "to improve",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[patient care]",
        placeholder: "[patient care]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "and streamline",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[medical processes]",
        placeholder: "[medical processes]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: ", ultimately enhancing",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: "[overall healthcare efficiency]",
        placeholder: "[overall healthcare efficiency]",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    questionId: 2,
    question: "Describe the technology or product.",
    contentList: [
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "Product: ",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: " [AI-Diagnose]",
        placeholder: "[InnovateX Solutions Inc.]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "Description: An ",
      },
      {
        contentType: "prompt",
        keyword: " [AI-driven diagnostic platform]",
        placeholder: "[AI-driven diagnostic platform]",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "Product: ",
      },
      {
        contentType: "text",
        content: "Product: ",
      },
    ],
  },
];

export const NewQAList = [
  {
    questionId: 1,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What is the full name of the company, and what is its core mission?",
    usecase: "common-question",
    answer: `Full Name: [Company Name].\nCore Mission: To [innovate/revolutionize/improve] the [industry] using [core technology/approach] to achieve [specific benefit]. Our mission focuses on [specific goal], ultimately enhancing [broad industry outcome]. We aim to achieve [specific target] by [specific year].`,
    madlibAnswer: `Full Name: [InnovateX Solutions Inc].\nCore Mission: To revolutionize [healthcare] using [AI-driven diagnostics] for [faster, more accurate results]. Our mission focuses on integrating [innovative technologies] to improve [patient care] and streamline [medical processes], ultimately enhancing [overall healthcare efficiency].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 2,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Describe the technology or product.",
    usecase: "common-question",
    answer:
      "Product Name: [Product Name] \n Description:A [software/platform/device/service] designed for [primary function]. It leverages [AI/IoT/cloud computing/big data] to provide [key benefits], improving [specific aspect] for [target audience]. The product has been implemented in [specific number] of [companies/industries] and has shown [specific result].",
  },
  {
    questionId: 3,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Describe the technical aspects and unique features. How does it innovate?",
    usecase: "common-question",
    answer: `• Technical Aspects:Uses [specific technologies/approaches] for [primary function]. The system processes [X] units per [time period], significantly reducing [time/cost/effort].\n• Unique Features: Includes [unique features such as high accuracy, fast processing, user-friendly interface], addressing [specific problem] and enhancing [desired outcome]. This results in [specific improvement], such as a [percentage] reduction in [errors/cost/time]. These features have led to a [specific percentage] increase in [efficiency/productivity].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 4,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Explain your business model and revenue streams.",
    usecase: "common-question",
    answer: `• Business Model: Operates on a [subscription-based/licensing/freemium/sales] model, offering [monthly/annual/one-time] plans.\n• Revenue Streams: Primary: [subscriptions/licenses/sales], Ancillary: [consulting services/data analytics/support services].\n• Stability and Growth: Over the past [time period], our [subscription base/customer base/revenue] has grown by [percentage], leading to a [percentage] increase in overall revenue. This growth is supported by [specific strategies or initiatives].
`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 5,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "common-question",
    question: "Provide key terms for the core technologies or features.",
    answer: `• Keywords: [Key terms related to your technologies/features]. Using these terms, we conducted a comprehensive prior art search, identifying over [number] relevant patents`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 6,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Describe specific patents or prior art encountered.",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `• Patents/Art:  We identified [Patent/Art Number], which utilizes a [similar/different] method/technology.\n• Similarities/Differences: It shares a similar [aspect], but differs in [another aspect], highlighting our unique approach. Our approach is differentiated by [specific unique feature].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 7,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How does your product meet novelty criteria?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Novelty Criteria: Our product uniquely combines [technology 1] with [technology 2] for [specific application], providing a novel approach to [problem/need]. This integration has not been seen in the market before and offers [specific advantage]. Our approach has been validated through [specific validation method]`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 8,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: " Why are the features non-obvious to professionals?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Non-obviousness: The integration of [technology 1] and [technology 2] for [application] requires specialized knowledge and innovative thinking, making it non-obvious to experts. This is evidenced by [specific evidence of innovation]. Our solution offers [specific benefit] that is not straightforward or expected.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 9,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How is the technology applicable to industrial needs?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Applicability: The technology enhances [specific function], meeting critical needs in [industry/setting], thus improving [efficiency/outcomes]. It has been adopted by [number] of [industries/companies], demonstrating its practicality and effectiveness. This has led to [specific improvement] in [specific metric].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 10,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What is your patent filing strategy?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Strategy: Filing in [US/EU/Asia/global markets] to secure broad protection across key markets, ensuring comprehensive IP coverage. We plan to file [number] of patents in [specific regions].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 11,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How have you ensured enablement in the patent application?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Enablement: Detailed descriptions and examples are included to fully demonstrate the technology. We have included [specific number] of examples to illustrate our claims.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 12,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How have you ensured the definiteness of claims in your patent application?",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Definiteness: Specific claims supported by data and examples, ensuring clear protection. Each claim is backed by [specific data or evidence].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 13,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: " Provide the exact claims in the patent application.",
    usecase: "ip-validity-analysis",
    answer: `Claims: Claims cover methods for [core technology] improving [specific function], highlighting innovation. For example, we claim [specific method or application].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 14,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What technologies are you licensing and why are they valuable?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Technologies: Licensing [specific technology/product] due to its [high accuracy/fast processing/cost efficiency/user-friendly interface], making it attractive to [types of companies]. It has been proven to [specific result or benefit]`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 15,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Who are your ideal licensees, and in which industries?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Ideal Licensees: [Types of organizations] in [industries] that benefit from our technology’s capabilities. Ideal licensees include [specific examples].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 16,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What are your business goals for licensing?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Goals: To expand market reach by [percentage] and generate additional revenue by [amount], helping us penetrate new markets. Our goal is to achieve [specific target] within [specific time frame].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 17,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What is your preferred licensing model?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Model: Prefer a [royalty-based/licensing/freemium] model for continuous revenue. This model has led to a [percentage] increase in revenue over the past [number] years.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 18,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What geographic regions are you targeting?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Regions: Targeting [regions] for significant market potential. We plan to focus on [specific countries or regions], which have shown a [percentage] increase in demand for similar technologies.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 19,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What are your financial expectations from licensing agreements?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Expectations: Expect annual royalties of [$X] based on market demand. We anticipate reaching this target by [specific year], based on projected growth rates of [percentage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 20,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How flexible are you in negotiating and managing licensing agreements?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Preparedness: We have an [experienced team] capable of adapting to various negotiation scenarios. Our team is skilled in [customizing agreements] to meet specific needs while ensuring mutual benefits`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 21,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What key terms and conditions are you prioritizing?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Key Terms: Prioritizing [exclusive rights/minimum sales requirements] for protecting interests and ensuring commitment. These terms have been agreed upon in [percentage] of our current agreements.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 22,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Are you open to strategic partnerships or cross-licensing opportunities?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Openness: Open to [strategic partnerships/cross-licensing] with complementary technologies. We have identified [number] potential partners in this regard.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 23,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What metrics and KPIs will you use to evaluate the success of your licensing strategy?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Metrics/KPIs: Use [revenue growth/market penetration] as key metrics. Over the past [number] years, these metrics have shown an average increase of [percentage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 24,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Do you have any performance requirements or specific expectations from licensees?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Requirements: Licensees must meet [performance metrics] and maintain [quality standards]. Compliance with these requirements has resulted in [percentage] fewer issues.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 25,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: " How do you plan to handle sublicensing rights, audit rights, and quality control?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Plan: Include specific clauses and regular checks to maintain IP integrity. We conduct audits [frequency] and have [percentage] compliance rate.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 26,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "Are there specific fields of use you are considering for licensing?",
    usecase: "ip-licensing-opportunity",
    answer: `Fields of Use: Focusing on [specific fields] aligned with our technology’s strengths. These fields have shown a growth rate of [percentage] in recent studies.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 27,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What is the pricing strategy for your product or service?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Pricing Strategy:  We use a [value-based/cost-plus/competitive] pricing strategy, setting the price at [$X]. This strategy has resulted in a [percentage] increase in sales over [time period].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 28,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How do you calculate the gross margin for your offerings?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Gross Margin Calculation: Calculated by subtracting [cost of goods sold] from [revenue], resulting in a [X%] gross margin.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 29,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What are the total development costs incurred for your product or service?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Development Costs: Estimated at [$X], covering [R&D, production, and testing]. Our investment in these areas has led to [specific result].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 30,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What future costs do you anticipate for full development and market launch?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Future Costs: Anticipate an additional [$X] for [marketing, distribution, and final enhancements]. These costs are expected to be recouped within [time frame].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 31,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What discount rate do you apply to future cash flows and why?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Discount Rate:  A [X%] discount rate, based on [industry standards and cost of capital]. This rate has been validated through [specific financial analysis].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 32,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What is the projected annual revenue growth rate, and how did you arrive at this figure?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Revenue Growth Rate: Projected at [X%], based on [market analysis and historical performance].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 33,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What are the anticipated operating expenses, and how are they allocated?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Operating Expenses: Include [staff salaries, R&D, marketing], totaling [X% of revenue].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 34,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How do you project sales revenue for your products or services over the next 5 years?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Sales Revenue Projections: Project annual sales of [$X] based on [market demand and expansion plans].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 35,
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What market and competitive analysis data have you gathered, and how does it influence your strategy?",
    usecase: "ip-valuation",
    answer: `Market Analysis: Analyzed [market size, growth rates, competitor strengths]. This data informs our strategic decisions and helps position our product effectively.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 36,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question: "What specific problem does your product or service solve for your target audience?",
    answer: `Problem Solved: Solves the problem of [specific problem], providing [key benefit]. This has resulted in [specific outcome].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 37,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question: "How does your product or service stand out from existing market offerings?",
    answer: `USP: Stands out due to [key features such as high accuracy, real-time analysis, user-friendly interface].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 38,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question: "What pricing strategy has your company adopted for its product or service?",
    answer: `Pricing Strategy: Adopted a [value-based/cost-plus/competitive] pricing strategy, pricing our product at [$X].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 39,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question: "What are the primary and potential secondary revenue streams for your company?",
    answer: `Revenue Streams: Primary: [product sales/subscriptions]; Secondary: [subscription services, data analytics, consulting].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 40,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question:
      "How is your company's cost structure organized, and what impact does it have on pricing and profitability?",
    answer: `Cost Structure: Organized to include [R&D, production, marketing], impacting our [pricing and gross margin of X%].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 41,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question: `Which sales and distribution channels is your company planning to use?`,
    answer: `Channels: Planning to use [direct sales, online platforms, partnerships with institutions].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 42,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-potential",
    question:
      " Who are your main competitors, and what differentiates your product or service from theirs?",
    answer: `Competitors: Main competitors are [Competitor A, Competitor B], and our product differentiates by [offering faster, more accurate results with specific integration].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 43,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question:
      "What internal metrics does your company use to measure success in aligning with market dynamics and industry trends?",
    answer: `Metrics: Use [market share growth, customer acquisition cost, user retention rates, innovation cycle times] as metrics. For example, our market share growth has been [percentage] annually.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 44,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question:
      "How does your company assess the impact of global market drivers and restraints on its product development and marketing strategies?",
    answer: `Assessment: Assess through [monitoring economic indicators, consumer trends, regulatory changes]. This has led to [specific strategic decision].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 45,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question:
      "Can you describe a recent strategic decision made by your company in response to projected market growth in your industry? What was the rationale behind this decision?",
    answer: `Decision: Made a strategic decision to [invest in new technology/expand into new markets] based on projected [market growth/consumer demand]. This decision resulted in [specific outcome].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 46,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question: "How does your company define its primary target market within its industry?",
    answer: `Target Market: Defines primary target market as [specific demographics/industry segments], focusing on [key characteristics/needs].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 47,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question: "What data-driven methods does your company use to segment its customer base?",
    answer: `Methods: Use [cluster analysis, demographic data, behavioral data] to create targeted marketing strategies and personalized product offerings. This approach has led to [specific outcome].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 48,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question:
      " What are the key factors that influence the purchasing decisions of your customers?",
    answer: `Factors: Key factors include [functionality, accuracy, design, value], influencing customer decisions directly.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 49,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question: "How has consumer feedback shaped the development of new features in your products?",
    answer: `Feedback: Feedback has led to the development of [enhanced features, new tools], ensuring products meet evolving needs. This has resulted in [specific improvement].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 50,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question:
      "Can you describe the competitive advantages of your latest product compared to its main competitors?",
    answer: `Advantages: Competitive advantages include [real-time assessment, adaptive algorithms], offering deeper insights and customization. These features have led to [specific market position].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 51,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "market-analysis",
    question: "What role does intellectual property play in your product differentiation strategy?",
    answer: `IP Role: Protects [unique technologies], maintaining competitive edge and preventing replication. Our IP portfolio includes [number] patents.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 52,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "m&a",
    question: "What are your strategic goals for mergers and acquisitions?",
    answer: `Goals: Strategic goals include [expanding market presence, acquiring new technologies, diversifying product offerings].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 53,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "m&a",
    question: "What criteria do you use to select acquisition targets?",
    answer: `Criteria: Select targets based on [financial health, technological innovation, market position].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 54,
    useCaseId: 1,
    usecase: "m&a",
    question: " Are there any regulatory considerations in your target markets?",
    answer: `Considerations: Consider [compliance with local regulations, intellectual property laws, industry standards].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 55,
    usecase: "m&a",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "What financial metrics do you consider important in assessing M&A targets?",
    answer: `Metrics: Consider [EBITDA, revenue growth, return on investment].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 56,
    usecase: "m&a",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: " How do you plan to integrate the acquired company into your operations?",
    answer: `Integration Plans: Plan to integrate by [aligning business processes, merging teams, consolidating technologies].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 57,
    usecase: "m&a",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question: "How do you measure the success of your M&A activities?",
    answer: `Success Measurement: Measure success through [financial performance, market expansion, synergy realization].`,
  },
  // m&a
  {
    questionId: 58,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the key factors that have contributed to changes in your company's market share over the past five years?",
    answer: `Factors: Key factors include [product innovation, marketing strategies, competitive actions], resulting in a market share growth of [percentage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 59,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Can you provide details on your company's brand positioning strategies and how they differ from those of your main competitors?",
    answer: `Strategies: Brand positioning focuses on [quality, innovation, customer-centricity], differentiating from competitors by [specific emphasis]. This has led to an increase in brand awareness by [percentage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 60,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      " Could you share insights into your company's financial performance trends, including revenue growth and profit margins, compared to your competitors?",
    answer: `Performance Trends: Revenue growth has been [X% annually], with profit margins [X% higher] than industry average. This trend has positioned us ahead of [specific competitors].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 61,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the most significant recent innovations your company has developed, and how do they compare to the innovations from your competitors?",
    answer: `Innovations: Recent innovations include [specific technologies], offering [higher accuracy/faster results], resulting in [specific benefits].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 62,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How does your company assess the effectiveness of its sales channels, and what unique strategies have you implemented compared to your competitors?",
    answer: `Effectiveness Assessment: Assess through [sales data analysis, customer feedback], implementing unique strategies such as [specific strategy], leading to a [percentage] increase in sales.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 63,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What unique aspects of your recent marketing campaigns have successfully engaged consumers, and how does this engagement compare to that achieved by your competitors?",
    answer: `Campaign Success: Focused on [personalized insights], achieving [higher engagement rates] compared to competitors, resulting in [percentage] more user interactions.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 64,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What strategic moves has your company recently made to stay competitive, and how do you anticipate these moves will position you against future competitor actions?",
    answer: `Strategic Moves: Invested in [R&D, AI integration], anticipating strengthened market position and enhanced competitive advantage.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 65,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Can you provide details on the strengths and weaknesses of your supply chain compared to those of your key competitors?",
    answer: `Supply Chain: Strengths include [robust relationships, efficient logistics], with weaknesses in [specific dependencies]. Our supply chain efficiency has led to a cost reduction of [percentage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 66,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What specific strategies has your company employed to enhance customer satisfaction, and how do these strategies compare to those of your competitors?",
    answer: `Customer Satisfaction: Strategies include [personalized support, continuous feedback loops], leading to [higher satisfaction rates] compared to competitors.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 67,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are some of the most impactful strategic alliances your company has formed, and how have these alliances affected your competitive positioning?",
    answer: `Alliances: Key alliances with [top institutions] have [enhanced credibility, expanded market reach], resulting in [specific competitive advantage].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 68,
    usecase: "competitive-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the most significant risks your company faces from competitive actions, and how are you managing these risks?",
    answer: `Risks: Significant risks include [new market entrants], managed by [investing in innovation, strengthening IP protection], resulting in [specific outcomes].`,
  },
  // Regulatory Pathways
  {
    questionId: 69,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Could you provide insights into the regulatory challenges and pathways in key markets such as the USA, EU, and Asia?",
    answer: `Challenges and Pathways: In the [USA], approval by [regulatory body] is required; in the [EU], compliance with [specific regulations] is essential; in [Asia], navigating [country-specific regulations] is crucial.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 70,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      " What operational adjustments has your company had to make to comply with international regulations?",
    answer: `Adjustments: Updated our [quality management systems, conducted staff training], and [implemented new processes] to ensure compliance with [specific regulations].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 71,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the major regulatory risks your company faces, and what mitigation strategies have you implemented?",
    answer: `Risks and Mitigations: Major risks include [delays in regulatory approval, changes in regulations], mitigated by [hiring regulatory experts, proactive compliance checks, strategic planning].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 72,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What quality management systems does your company implement to satisfy regulatory requirements?",
    answer: `Quality Systems: Implement [ISO standards, GMP standards], ensuring compliance with [specific regulations] and maintaining high-quality standards.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 73,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What emerging regulatory trends could potentially impact your market, and how do you plan to respond?",
    answer: `Trends and Responses: Trends include [increased data privacy regulations, stricter environmental regulations], and we plan to respond by [enhancing data security measures, improving sustainability practices].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 74,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the current regulatory challenges your company is facing, and how are these affecting your operations?",
    answer: `Challenges: Facing challenges in [adapting to new regulatory updates, ensuring compliance across multiple regions], affecting [time-to-market, operational costs].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 75,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are your company's future targets in terms of regulatory achievements, and what steps are you taking to meet these goals?",
    answer: `Targets and Steps: Future targets include [achieving regulatory approval in additional markets, maintaining compliance with evolving regulations], with steps such as [expanding our regulatory team, continuous monitoring of regulatory changes].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 76,
    usecase: "regulatory-pathways",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How does your company engage with regulatory bodies to ensure compliance and influence regulatory frameworks?",
    answer: `Engagement: Engage through [regular consultations, participation in industry forums, collaboration with regulatory authorities], ensuring proactive compliance and influencing regulatory developments.`,
  },
  // Consumer Intelligence
  {
    questionId: 77,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are your strategic goals for expanding into new demographic or geographic markets in the next 5 years?",
    answer: `Goals: Expanding into [specific regions/markets] and targeting [specific demographics], aiming to increase market share by [percentage] and revenue by [amount].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 78,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      " What consumer trends and behaviors have you identified as pivotal for shaping your product development over the next few years?",
    answer: `Trends and Behaviors: Trends include [increased use of health monitoring apps], shaping our focus on [integration with wearable devices]. Understanding these trends helps us align our [product development] with market demands.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 79,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How do you plan to leverage digital marketing to increase consumer engagement in underpenetrated markets?",
    answer: `Digital Marketing: Plan to use [targeted social media campaigns, influencer partnerships, content marketing] to increase engagement by [percentage] in underpenetrated markets.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 80,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the anticipated challenges in adopting new technologies among your target consumers, and how do you plan to address them?",
    answer: `Challenges: Anticipated challenges include [technology acceptance, data privacy concerns], addressed by [user education programs, implementing robust security measures].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 81,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How do you intend to measure the success of new market entries and product launches?",
    answer: `Measurement: Measure success by [sales figures, market share growth, customer feedback], aiming for a [percentage] increase in sales within [time frame].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 82,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What strategies will you implement to enhance customer loyalty and retention in increasingly competitive markets?",
    answer: `Strategies: Implement [loyalty programs, personalized customer support, regular updates], aiming to increase customer retention by [percentage] over [time frame].`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 83,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Can you describe how you will use consumer feedback to inform future product iterations and service improvements?",
    answer: `Feedback Use: Use [surveys, focus groups, online reviews] to gather feedback, leading to the development of [new features, improved services] and enhancing customer satisfaction.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 84,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are your plans for integrating emerging technologies to stay ahead in your market?",
    answer: `Emerging Technologies: Plans include integrating [AI, IoT, blockchain] to enhance product functionality and user experience, aiming to stay ahead of competitors.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 85,
    usecase: "consumer-landscape",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How will you adapt your pricing strategy to balance between growth, competitiveness, and profitability in new markets?",
    answer: `Pricing Strategy: Adapt pricing strategy using [tiered pricing models, promotional discounts], aiming to attract new customers while maintaining profitability.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 86,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Can you provide an overview of your business model and how your product or technology integrates within it?",
    answer: `Business Model and Integration: Our business operates on a [subscription-based/licensing/sales] model, focusing on [industry or market]. The [product/technology] contributes [X%] to our total revenue, offering [specific functionalities] that enhance [specific business operations or customer experience]. This integration has led to a [Y%] increase in customer retention and a [Z%] reduction in operational costs.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 87,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the core technologies and innovations in your product, and how do they differentiate from existing solutions in the market?",
    answer: `Core Technologies: Our product leverages [technology 1, technology 2] to achieve [specific outcomes]. These innovations differentiate us from competitors by [unique features or approaches], such as [specific technological advancements or efficiencies]. For instance, our use of [specific technology] has resulted in a [A%] improvement in performance compared to the industry average.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 88,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What has been your product development process, and what key milestones have you achieved?",
    answer: `Development Process: The development process involved [research phases, prototype development, testing stages], resulting in key milestones such as [initial prototype completion in month/year], beta testing with [X] users, and market launch in [month/year]. These milestones reflect our progress in [specific areas] and have contributed to achieving [B%] market penetration within [C] months of launch.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 89,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What patents have you identified as potentially relevant to your technology, and what are their key claims?",
    answer: `Relevant Patents: We have identified [Patent Number 1, Patent Number 2], with key claims focusing on [specific technological aspects]. These patents could potentially impact our FTO analysis due to [similarities/differences] in [specific features or methods]. For example, [Patent Number 1] claims [specific method], which overlaps [D%] with our [specific feature].
`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 90,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How does your internal patent portfolio and IP strategy support your product's development and commercialization?",
    answer: `Internal Patent Portfolio: Our portfolio includes [number] patents covering [specific technologies or methods]. Our IP strategy focuses on [protecting core technologies, preventing infringement], which supports our product by providing [specific strategic benefits]. Our patents have contributed to a [E%] increase in market share and a [F%] reduction in legal disputes over the past [G] years.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 91,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How do your product's technical specifications and novel features distinguish it from existing patents?",
    answer: `Technical Differentiation: Our product's technical specifications include [detailed technical features], which distinguish it from existing patents by [unique aspects]. The novelty lies in [specific innovative approaches or integrations], resulting in [H%] better efficiency and [I%] cost savings compared to existing solutions.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 92,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are the potential infringement risks identified, and how do they relate to your product's key features?",
    answer: `Infringement Risks: Potential risks include [specific patents] that cover [similar aspects]. These risks relate to our key features such as [feature 1, feature 2], which may overlap with the claims of [Patent Number 1]. The overlap risk is estimated at [J%], based on a detailed comparison of claims and features.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 93,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "Have you explored design-around options or alternative technologies to mitigate potential infringement risks?",
    answer: `Design Around Options: We have explored alternatives such as [design modifications, using different technologies] to mitigate risks. For example, instead of [specific method], we use [alternative method], which reduces infringement risk by [K%] and maintains [L%] of the original functionality.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 94,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "How does your product fit into the current market and competitive landscape, and what challenges do you anticipate?",
    answer: `Market Fit: Our product fits into the market by [solving specific problems, meeting specific needs]. The competitive landscape includes [main competitors], and we anticipate challenges such as [market acceptance, competitive actions]. Our market analysis shows a [M%] market growth rate, with our product expected to capture [N%] of the market share within [O] years.`,
  },
  {
    questionId: 95,
    usecase: "freedom-to-operate",
    useCaseId: 1,
    question:
      "What are your future development plans for your product, and how will your IP strategy evolve to support these plans?",
    answer: `Future Development: Plans include [expanding features, entering new markets], supported by evolving our IP strategy to [file additional patents, strengthen existing protections]. This ensures we remain competitive and compliant with FTO requirements. Our projections show that these developments will result in a [P%] increase in revenue and a [Q%] expansion in market reach over the next [R] years.`,
  },
];
